( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
I guessed you didn't have much of an appetite.
أظن أنك لم تكن لديك شهية كبيرة.
That's why I prepared a few more dishes.
لهذا السبب قمت بإعداد المزيد من الأطباق.
Come on, eat up.
هيا، تناول الطعام.
It seems
يبدو
you no longer want this.
لم تعد ترغب في هذا.
If you're willing to have breakfast without being fussy,
إذا كنت ترغب في تناول وجبة الإفطار دون أن تكون متطلباً،
I can give you a chance
أستطيع أن أمنحك فرصة
to obtain this key from me.
للحصول على هذا المفتاح مني.
I'm done.
أنا انتهيت.
You didn't say that I had to finish everything.
لم تقل إنه يجب عليّ إنهاء كل شيء.
Fine.
بخير.
But you only have one minute.
لكن لديك دقيقة واحدة فقط.
Five seconds have already passed.
لقد مرت خمس ثوانٍ بالفعل.
What a shame.
يا للعار.
Game over.
انتهت اللعبة.
Take a few more bites.
تناول بضع لقمات أخرى.
If so, I'll give you a few more seconds to get it, okay?
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فسأمنحك بضع ثوانٍ أخرى للحصول عليه، حسناً؟
You really don't take care of yourself.
أنت لا تعتني بنفسك حقاً.
But that's fine.
لكن لا بأس بذلك.
No matter how much of a tantrum you throw,
مهما بلغت نوبة غضبك،
it doesn't affect my feelings for you.
هذا لا يؤثر على مشاعري تجاهك.
Didn't I do a good job just now?
ألم أقم بعمل جيد الآن؟
Don't you think I deserve at least ten minutes
ألا تعتقد أنني أستحق عشر دقائق على الأقل؟
of you toying with me while I find the key?
هل تتلاعب بي بينما أبحث عن المفتاح؟
[Chen Qicheng] 11 A.M.
[تشن كيتشنغ] الساعة 11 صباحًا
Meet at Cat Ears Cafe.
التقوا في مقهى آذان القط.
I need to head outside.
أحتاج للخروج.
Stay home and behave yourself.
ابقَ في المنزل والتزم بحسن السلوك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I'll be taking the two fragments with me.
سآخذ القطعتين معي.
If you run away from home
إذا هربت من المنزل
while I'm away,
أثناء غيابي،
I'll have no choice but to destroy them.
لن يكون أمامي خيار سوى تدميرهم.
You won't destroy them.
لن تدمرهم.
It depends on your performance.
الأمر يعتمد على أدائك.
As long as you're here,
طالما أنت هنا،
nothing can kill me anyway.
لا شيء يستطيع قتلي على أي حال.
As for the lives of others,
أما بالنسبة لحياة الآخرين،
what has that got to do with me?
ما علاقة ذلك بي؟
You texted me and told me
أرسلت لي رسالة نصية وأخبرتني
that Wu Siyuan wanted you to tell me the truth behind my parents' death.
أن وو سييوان أراد منك أن تخبرني بالحقيقة وراء وفاة والديّ.
So,
لذا،
was he really responsible for their deaths?
هل كان هو المسؤول حقاً عن وفاتهم؟
Mr. Wu was merely executing orders.
كان السيد وو ينفذ الأوامر فحسب.
The person who really gave the orders
الشخص الذي أصدر الأوامر بالفعل
was Director Xia.
كان المخرج شيا.
The Affinity B Virus inside you
فيروس أفينيتي بي بداخلك
is inherently more active than in ordinary Ren.
هو بطبيعته أكثر نشاطًا من رين العادي.
Director Xia had high hopes for you.
كان لدى المخرج شيا آمال كبيرة فيك.
She said
قالت
she'd have you, one way or another.
ستستحوذ عليك، بطريقة أو بأخرى.
We wanted to take you peacefully.
أردنا أن نأخذك بسلام.
But your parents refused to comply.
لكن والديك رفضا الامتثال.
No matter how many times you come,
مهما تكررت زياراتك،
the answer will always be the same.
ستكون الإجابة دائماً هي نفسها.
No means no.
لا تعني لا.
Time for you to leave.
حان وقت رحيلك.
How annoying.
يا له من أمر مزعج.
If you don't cooperate with us,
إذا لم تتعاون معنا،
we'll take him away by force.
سنأخذه بالقوة.
The Ren who was on the mission with me
رين الذي كان معي في المهمة
suddenly went berserk and killed your parents.
فجأةً أصيب بالجنون وقتل والديك.
Following Director Xia's orders,
امتثالاً لأوامر المدير شيا،
I sent him back to the bureau first.
أعدته إلى المكتب أولاً.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
Director Xia sent Mr. Wu there to clean up the mess.
أرسل المدير شيا السيد وو إلى هناك لتنظيف الفوضى.
He took you away in the suspect's name.
لقد أخذك بعيداً باسم المشتبه به.
Following Director Xia's orders,
امتثالاً لأوامر المدير شيا،
Mr. Wu then began conducting covert training for you.
ثم بدأ السيد وو بإجراء تدريب سري لك.
My time is running out.
وقتي ينفد.
I have to say this,
لا بد لي من قول هذا،
or I'll die with regrets.
وإلا سأموت وأنا نادم.
The password to Li Xiang's phone
كلمة مرور هاتف لي شيانغ
should be Siyuan's birthday.
ينبغي أن يكون عيد ميلاد سيوان.
[Swipe up to use Face ID or enter your passcode]
[اسحب لأعلى لاستخدام ميزة التعرف على الوجه أو أدخل رمز المرور الخاص بك]
[sweet]
[حلو]
[Delivered  From: Xie Xinxu]
[تم التسليم من: شيه شينكسو]
[Tracking Number: 762C 6843 00832]
[رقم التتبع: 762C 6843 00832]
[Recipient: Wu Nongyu] What is this?
[المستلم: وو نونغيو] ما هذا؟
No idea. Your package.
لا أعرف. طردك.
Xie Xinxu's real purpose in approaching you.
ما هو الهدف الحقيقي من تقرب شي شينكسو منك؟
It was only to get revenge on me.
كان ذلك فقط للانتقام مني.
It's dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير.
You stay here.
ستبقى هنا.
I'll look for him.
سأبحث عنه.
You were the one who sent the training video to me.
أنت من أرسلت لي الفيديو التدريبي.
So, has this all been part of your plan from the beginning?
إذن، هل كان كل هذا جزءًا من خطتك منذ البداية؟
You drove Siyuan and me apart
لقد فرّقتَ بيني وبين سيوان.
to get your revenge.
للانتقام.
How should I describe my current feelings?
كيف أصف مشاعري الحالية؟
It felt like I had used my best technique
شعرت وكأنني استخدمت أفضل تقنياتي
to toss
للرمي
a carefully chosen pebble onto the water.
حصاة مختارة بعناية على الماء.
I watched it
لقد شاهدته
skip lightly across the surface,
انزلق بخفة على السطح،
leaving behind one,
تاركاً وراءه واحداً،
two,
اثنين،
then many beautiful arcs...
ثم العديد من الأقواس الجميلة...
You never intended to rescue him from the start, right?
لم تكن تنوي إنقاذه منذ البداية، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
Your brother did so many terrible things.
لقد فعل أخوك أشياءً فظيعة كثيرة.
Didn't he deserve to die?
ألم يكن يستحق الموت؟
But in the end,
لكن في النهاية،
it still
لا يزال
has to sink.
يجب أن يغرق.
Luckily, you found out in time.
لحسن الحظ، اكتشفت الأمر في الوقت المناسب.
If not,
وإلا،
she would've died from carbon monoxide poisoning.
كانت ستموت بسبب التسمم بأول أكسيد الكربون.
Mr. Ding,
السيد دينغ،
tell me.
أخبرني.
Did she do this on purpose?
هل فعلت ذلك عن قصد؟
Did she try to leave me by hurting herself on purpose?
هل حاولت تركي بإيذاء نفسها عمداً؟
Her condition hasn't been stabilized yet.
لم تستقر حالتها بعد.
The virus in her body
الفيروس في جسدها
is attacking her immune system relentlessly.
يهاجم جهازها المناعي بلا هوادة.
If her fever doesn't subside,
إذا لم تنخفض حرارتها،
she won't last for long.
لن تدوم طويلاً.
Mr. Ding,
السيد دينغ،
is there any other way to save her?
هل هناك أي طريقة أخرى لإنقاذها؟
I suggest that you two form a pact immediately.
أقترح أن تعقدا اتفاقاً على الفور.
Use the high concentration of Affinity B Virus within your body
استخدم التركيز العالي لفيروس Affinity B داخل جسمك
to suppress the Affinity A Virus in her body.
لقمع فيروس Affinity A في جسدها.
But in her current condition,
لكن في حالتها الحالية،
there's no way
لا سبيل
we can form a normal pact.
يمكننا إبرام اتفاق عادي.
Perhaps
ربما
you two can exchange your blood.
بإمكانكما تبادل دمائكما.
[Affinity A Virus Concentration Monitoring]
[مراقبة تركيز فيروس Affinity A]
[10^8 cp/mL Exceeds Safety Limit]
[10^8 cp/mL يتجاوز الحد الآمن]
[Affinity A Virus Concentration Monitoring 10^10 cp/mL High-Risk Alert]
[مراقبة تركيز فيروس Affinity A 10^10 cp/mL تنبيه عالي الخطورة]
Why isn't this working...?
لماذا لا يعمل هذا؟
Nongyu?
نونجيو؟
Nongyu...
نونجيو...
[Affinity A Virus Concentration Monitoring 10^10 cp/mL High-Risk Alert]
[مراقبة تركيز فيروس Affinity A 10^10 cp/mL تنبيه عالي الخطورة]
Wake up.
استيقظ.
It must be that the viral concentration isn't high enough.
لا بد أن تركيز الفيروس ليس مرتفعاً بما فيه الكفاية.
[Affinity A Virus Concentration Monitoring 10^6 cp/mL Safe]
[مراقبة تركيز الفيروس من النوع أ 10^6 نسخة/مل آمن]
Thank you for staying.
شكراً لكم على إقامتكم.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for coming back.
لعودتك.